https://www.heatmat.co.uk/privacy-statement/

Privacy StatementWho we areIn this privacy policy references to "we", "us" and "our" are to Heat Mat Limited. References to "our Website" or "the Website" are to www.heatmat.co.uk.What information we collect and how:We only process personal data lawfully for the legitimate purpose it is intended and we will be transparent with the reason for collection of data via our website.The information we collect via the Website may include:Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive marketing email updates on products and offers).Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website.Data recorded by the Website, which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings, this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on your computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browsers 'help' facility. What we do with your informationAny personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018 and other applicable laws as follows:We will use the details you provide to process your request and in rare cases to provide after sales service.In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information on our other products and services. In such a case you will be offered the option to opt in/out before completing your purchase. We will not use your email address to send you information on our other products and services unless you have clearly provided us with permission to do so. You will always be offered the option to opt-out of any further communication. Any details you provide to us via a Warranty Registration form will only be used to contact you in conjunction with your warranty and the associated products.We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes and we will never share your information for marketing reasons unless consent to do so is provided.Your RightsYou have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address to the following address:PrivacyHeat Mat Limited3 Danworth Farm,Cuckfield Road,Hurstpierpoint,West SussexBN6 9GLUKOther WebsitesThis privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.Contact usIf you have any questions regarding our privacy policy and the use of your data please contact us via sales@heatmat.co.uk, call 01444 247020 or write to us at the above address.
Click Here For Our 2020 BrochureWe've updated our product brochure.Click Here to View
Heat Mat Messenger
Open Heat Mat Messenger
×
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
×
TitlePlease selectMrMrsMsMissDrFirst name*Last name*Your phone number*Your email address*
Postcode*Project timeframe7 daysWithin 2 weeksWithin 1 monthWithin 3 monthsWithin 6 monthsMore than 6 monthsBusiness typeArchitectBuilderElectricianHome ownerPlumberRetailerTilerOtherBusiness nameRoom detailsRoom 1 type*Please selectLiving roomKitchenBathroomEn-suiteWet roomBedroomConservatoryOtherRoom 1 floor size (in m²)*Room 2 type*Please selectLiving roomKitchenBathroomEn-suiteWet roomBedroomConservatoryOtherRoom 2 floor size (in m²)*Room 3 type*Please selectLiving roomKitchenBathroomEn-suiteWet roomBedroomConservatoryOtherRoom 3 floor size (in m²)*Which products do you require?*Please selectUnderfloor heatingMirror demistersThermostatsMultipleUnknownIs screed being laid?*Please selectYesNoDon't knowPlease provide further information so we can calculate the best possible system for the best price:
If known, what is the subfloor type e.g. Floorboards or Concrete?
If known, what is the final floor covering e.g. Carpet, Wood, Laminate*
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
×
